so this is actually number 92
everybody's last I was 91
so Apple number 92 there's a lot of
times when I go out of house to buy a
specific item very specific item and I
don't know where to go for it and if
it's something like passport photos you
can google it you usually find a place
near you but things that are a little
more intricate I need a little small
empty thread I need whatever it happens
to be then to know where you can buy
that and everywhere you can buy that so
you can combine your your errands to do
the fewest amount an errand mapping map
it also helps you know what everything
is it's crowd-sourced so either the
store itself can put those things on
there you can how did that informations
already there and available we can also
add the pricing so you can see with the
price of gas and the price of your time
is it more useful to go to one location
and do all of your shopping if I might
pay a slightly higher price or go to
these 10 different locations so a arond
mapping map is number 92